We've seen that you can control the behavior of a convolutional layer
我们刚刚学到可以通过指定过滤器数量和每个过滤器的大小
by specifying the number of filters and the size of each filter.
控制卷积层的行为
For instance, to increase the number of nodes in
例如 要增加卷积层中的节点数量
a convolutional layer you could increase the number of filters.
你可以增加过滤器数量
To increase the size of the detected patterns you could increase the size of your filter.
要增大所检测过滤器的大小 你可以增大过滤器的大小
But there are even more hyper parameters that you can do.
但是还有更多超参数
One of these hyper parameters is referred to as the stride of the convolution.
其中一个就是卷积的 stride
The stride is just the amount by which the filter slides over the image.
stride 是指过滤器在图片上每次滑动时移动的距离(用像素数量表示)
In the example in the previous video the stride was one and we
在上个视频中的示例中 stride 是 1
moved the convolution window horizontally and vertically across the image,
我们在图片上水平和垂直地移动卷积窗
one pixel at a time.
一次移动一个像素
A stride of one makes the convolutional layer
stride 1 使卷积层
roughly the same width and height as the input image.
和输入图片的宽和高差不多
In this animation, we've drawn the purple convolutional layer as stacked feature maps.
在此动画中 我们用紫色卷积层表示堆叠特征映射
If we instead make the stride equal to two,
如果让 stride 等于 2
the convolutional layer is about half of the width and height of the image.
卷积层就大约等于图片宽和高的一半
I save roughly because it depends on what you do at the edge of your image.
说大约等于是因为它取决于你对图片边缘的处理
To see how the treatment of the edges will matter,
要了解边缘处理带来的影响
consider our toy example of a 5x5 grayscale image.
看看这个 5x5 灰度图片小例子
Say we have a different filter now with the height and width of two,
假设现在有个不同的过滤器 宽和高是 2
say the stride is also two,
stride 也是 2
then as before we start with the filter and the top left corner of
和之前一样 我们让过滤器从图片左上角开始
the image and calculate the value for the first node and the convolutional layer.
计算卷积层中第一个节点的值
We then move the filter two units to the right and do the same.
然后让过滤器向右移动两个单元 并执行相同的操作
But when we move the filter two more units to the right,
但是当我们让过滤器再向右移动两个单元时
the filter extends outside the image.
过滤器跑到图片外面了
What do we do now?
现在该怎么办？
Do we still want to keep the corresponding convolutional node?
还保留对应的卷积节点吗？
For now, let's just populate the places where the filter
暂时先用问号填充
extends outside with a question mark and proceed as planned.
过滤器跑到图片外的位置 并按计划继续
So now, how do we deal with these nodes where the filter extended outside the image?
现在如何处理过滤器跑到图片外的这些节点？
We could as a first option just get rid of them.
第一种选择是直接删掉它们
Note that if we choose this option it's possible that
注意 如果这么做的话
our convolutional layer has no information about some regions of the image.
我们的卷积层可能就没有图片中某些区域的信息
This is the case here for the right and bottom edges of the image.
这个图片的右侧和底部边缘就是这种情况
As a second option,
第二种选择是
we could plan ahead for this case by padding the image with
我们可以提前规划 在图片边缘填充 0
zeros to give the filter more space to move.
让过滤器有更多的移动空间
Now when we populate the convolutional layer we
现在当我们填充卷积层时
get contributions from every region in the image.
就可以获得图片中每个区域的信息了
We can specify which option we'd like to be the case
我们可以通过为卷积层设定填充
by setting what's known as the padding for our convolutional layer.
来指定选择哪个选项
If you prefer the first case where you're okay with
如果你选择第一个选项
potentially losing some nodes in the convolutional layer,
能够接受卷积层可能会丢失信息
you'll set your padding to 'valid.'
则将填充设为 'valid'
On the other hand, if you prefer the second case,
另一方面 如果选择第二种情形
you'll set your padding to 'same.'
则将填充设为 'same'
If you'd like more details about padding,
如果你想详细了解填充
you're encouraged to check out the optional reading below.
请参阅下方的可选阅读资料
In the next lesson we show you how to pass
在下节课 我们将演示
these arguments into Keras when tuning your convolutional layers.
在调试卷积层时 如何向 Keras 传入这些参数